import automobile from "./../../audio/listeningTask/automobile.mp3";
import boot from "./../../audio/listeningTask/boot.mp3";
import breakfast from "./../../audio/listeningTask/breakfast.mp3";
import button from "./../../audio/listeningTask/button.mp3";
import candle from "./../../audio/listeningTask/candle.mp3";
import chest from "./../../audio/listeningTask/chest.mp3";
import chicken from "./../../audio/listeningTask/chicken.mp3";
import childhood from "./../../audio/listeningTask/childhood.mp3";
import doctor from "./../../audio/listeningTask/doctor.mp3";
import game from "./../../audio/listeningTask/game.mp3";
import jacket from "./../../audio/listeningTask/jacket.mp3";
import morning from "./../../audio/listeningTask/morning.mp3";
import mother from "./../../audio/listeningTask/mother.mp3";
import night from "./../../audio/listeningTask/night.mp3";
import sound from "./../../audio/listeningTask/sound.mp3";
import stone from "./../../audio/listeningTask/stone.mp3";
import ticket from "./../../audio/listeningTask/ticket.mp3";
import vocabulary from "./../../audio/listeningTask/vocabulary.mp3";

const listeningTask = {
  title: "Аудирование",
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: automobile,
      correctAnswer: ["automobile"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: boot,
      correctAnswer: ["boot"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: breakfast,
      correctAnswer: ["breakfast"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: button,
      correctAnswer: ["button"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: candle,
      correctAnswer: ["candle"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: chest,
      correctAnswer: ["chest"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: chicken,
      correctAnswer: ["chicken"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: childhood,
      correctAnswer: ["childhood"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: doctor,
      correctAnswer: ["doctor"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: game,
      correctAnswer: ["game"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: jacket,
      correctAnswer: ["jacket"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: morning,
      correctAnswer: ["morning"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: mother,
      correctAnswer: ["mother"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: night,
      correctAnswer: ["night"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: sound,
      correctAnswer: ["sound"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: stone,
      correctAnswer: ["stone"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: ticket,
      correctAnswer: ["ticket"]
    },
    {
      question: "Write listened english word",
      audio: vocabulary,
      correctAnswer: ["vocabulary"]
    }
  ]
};
export default listeningTask;
